http://www.systemsmanager.net/privacy-policy/

The Most Valuable Real Estate On Your WebSite
7 Sure-Fire Ways to Keep Your Customers Coming Back For More!
The Most Valuable Real Estate On Your WebSite
7 Sure-Fire Ways to Keep Your Customers Coming Back For More!
Who we are
Our website address is: http://www.systemsmanager.net.
What personal data we collect and why we collect it
This online privacy policy discloses SystemsManager Technologies online information gathering practices and describes the usage of the information gathered on this website.
-Personal Information Collection and Use The only personally identifiable information collected on this site is submitted to us freely and deliberately by site users. We collect and use this information in the following ways:
– Contact Us We collect your contact information through our ‘Contact’ form so that we can respond to your requests. We may keep this information in a database. You may bypass the form submission if you wish by using the e-mail address provided and by using your personal mail application to submit your request.
– Apply for a job When applying for a job using the online form, the data you submit is stored in a secure database. We have taken careful measures to ensure the integrity and security of your data. It is stored behind a firewall and is only accessible by using a secure ID and password which is distributed to human resources staff or website staff members who need it to do their jobs.
– Apply for a partnership When submitting company information about a partnership, this information is e-mailed directly to an SystemsManager Technologies partnership representative. It may also be stored in a secure database.
– Email SystemsManager Technologies will not share e-mail addresses or contact information we collect through our website with any third parties unless required by law. If you send us an e- mail message, we may keep that message, your e-mail address, and any other data submitted with the message.
-Cookies SystemsManager Technologies uses cookies on this website. We utilize cookie technology to enhance and customize your experience. Cookies contain no personally identifying information. We use cookies for the following:
* We track your visited pages in order to provide the ‘Frequently Visited Areas’ navigation
* We store the polls you have responded to, however we do not store your answers
* We store the jobs search criteria, however we do not store which jobs you review
* We store your homepage selection
-Server logs Server logs capture certain non- personally identifying data, such as the time and date of a web visit, the browser and operating system being used, the IP address or domain name of the user’s ISP, and the web URL a user linked from. This information is used generally to help us plan system enhancements when necessary and to provide content which is compatible with our visitors’ web browsing systems.
-Searches Keyword search function is provided in the press release area of the SystemsManager Technologies website as a convenience to our users. We do not collect your name or e- mail address as a result of using a search feature, nor do we tabulate search terms entered by individuals.
-Hyperlinks to Other Web Sites SystemsManager Technologies includes links to websites of other companies. We do not log visitors’ clicks from our site to other sites. Please note that we take no responsibility for the content of any external web site.
– Security We have taken careful measures to ensure the integrity and security of your data. It is stored behind a firewall and is only accessible by using a secure ID and password which is distributed to staff members who need it to do their jobs.
Acceptance of SystemsManager Technologies Online Privacy Policy By using this site, you agree to SystemsManager Technologies online privacy policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use this site. We may change or modify this policy without notice, please check back periodically.
Copyright 2020
SystemsManager Technologies
We use cookies to ensure that we give you the best experience on our website. If you continue to use this site we will assume that you are happy with it.OkPrivacy policy
